老爸老妈的罗漫史\n第1季 第13集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother\nSeason 01 Episode 13
孩子们, 生活中有很多浪漫的时刻
Kids,in life there are a lot of big romantic moments.
这让生活更精彩
And they make life worth living
但问题是
but here's the problem:
浪漫过后
Moments pass,
潜伏在角落里的是个满面胡子残酷的
and lurking just around the corner from those moments
名叫现实的家伙
is a cruel,unshaven bastard named reality.
那么, 回溯到2006年
And so,back in 2006,
Claudia和Stuart婚礼的那个晚上
on the night of Claudia and Stuart's wedding,
现实就是敌人
reality was the enemy.
（美国的）和平队?
The Peace Corps?
我明天出航 时间两年
I ship out tomorrow two years.
你知道, 有些人说参加和平队是一个人能做的最高尚的事
You know,some people say the Peace Corps is\nthe most noble thing a person can do.
对这些人, 我会问 "是吗?"
To those people,I say,"is it?"
一般他们会答 "对, 是的"
And usually they say,"yes,it is."
Barney, 他们是对的
Barney,they are so right.
我希望我也能做点什么
I wish there was something I could do.
噢 Tanya...
Oh Tanya...
我很高兴你能这么说
I'm so glad you said that.
这不是我预期的的一晚
This wasn't how I'd thought the night would\nturn out.
今晚应该是我和Robin共渡的浪漫时刻
This was finally supposed to be my big moment with Robin.
但是现实随后而来
But then reality came along.
Robin在最后一分钟被叫去代播11点新闻
Robin got called up last minute to anchor\nthe 11:00 news.
那是她事业的大突破
It was her big break.
我只好一个人去婚礼
And I went to the wedding stag.
然后, 当我期待着至少...
Then, when I least expected it...
你昨晚干嘛去了?
where the hell did you disappear to last night?
我渡过了最难忘的一晚
I had the most amazing night ever.
说来听听
Tell me about it.
那蛋糕
That cake.
是我吃过的最棒的蛋糕
Best cake I ever had.
说真的
Seriously.
我的胃象在说 "嘿, 伙计"
My stomach was,like,"hey,bro,"
不知道你在吃什么
I don't know what you're eating,
因为我没长眼睛
cause I don't have any eyes,
但是这真的很棒
but it's basically awesome,
多送点来食管"
so keep sending it down gullet alley."
我知道
I know.
我的胃像在说
My stomach was,like,
"女朋友, 我们不是一直相处的和睦\n但那蛋糕..."
"girlfriend,we don't always get along,\nbut that cake..."
Lily\nLily.
对了
right.
"有史来最美妙的一晚" 说吧
"Most amazing night ever," and go.
你知道, 我得告诉你, 我有个原则
You know,I should tell you,I have a rule.
我向来不在婚礼上找伴
I never hook up at weddings.
我猜你不是一直都坚守原则
I'm guessing you haven't always had this rule.
因为, 这些浪漫时刻
here's the thing,those big romantic moments,
经历的时候很棒
they're great when they happen,
但它们并不现实
but they're not real.
是啊, 是啊，就像,就像，现在\nExactly,exactly，like，like just now,
当我看见你在那边跳小鸡舞时
when I saw you doing the chicken dance out there,
我不会说谎骗你
I'm not gonna lie to you,
当时我象被电闪了
big time thunderbolt.
你应该看我跳踢踏舞
You should see me tap dance.
你会跪地哀求
You'd be down on bended knee.
还好没有疯狂
Sadly not out of character.
但我知道这只是幻觉
But I know now it's just a mirage.
婚礼幻视
Wedding goggles.
正确
Exactly.
所以, 简单的说
And that,in a nutshell,
这就是为什么我不会对你采取进一步行动
is why I'm not putting the moves on you.
现在这不是你的行动吗?
This isn't the moves?
什么, 你...
What,you...
你觉得这是吗?
you think this is the moves?
相信我, 你知道什么是真正的行动
Believe me,you'd know the moves.
那么10桌外的人们也知道了
People ten tables away would know the moves.
这太糟了
that's too bad.
说来听听
Tell me about it.
你知道, 我认为...
You know,I think...
我有解决办法
I have a solution.
有意思
Interested.
首先
And to preface this,
我们今晚不会上床
we're not gonna sleep together tonight.
没那么有趣了
Less interested.
继续
go ahead.
好的
Okay.
所以一般搞砸的会是第二次见面
So the thing that always screws it up is \nthe next day.
是吗?
Right?
那么...
So...
为什么我们不直接把那部分去掉呢?
why don't we just cut that part out?
你的意思是?
What are you saying?
我是说, 我在这儿, 你也在这儿
I'm saying,I'm here,you're here,
这是个盛大的婚礼
this is a big romantic wedding
为什么我们不跳跳舞共渡美妙时光
why don't we just dance and have a great time,
然后结束后\n不要再见面
and then when it's over,\nnever see each other again.
除非...
Unless...
不 没有除非
no. No unless.
不留e-mail, 不留电话甚至不留姓名
No e-mails,no phone numbers,not even names.
今晚我们将有一个永不磨灭的回忆
Tonight we will make a memory that will never be tarnished.
然后...
And then...
当我们老去时
when we're old and gray,
回想今晚
we'll look back on this night
将是完美的一晚
and it'll be perfect.
好吧, 我参加
Okay,I'm in.
好的
Okay.
我想, 我们得有假名?
I guess,what,we'll need fake names?
你可以叫我奶油花
you can call me Buttercup.
很高兴认识你, 奶油花
Pleased to meet you,Buttercup.
我叫... Lando Calrissian\n（星战里面的赌徒无赖）
I'm... Lando Calrissian.
这有点让人激动
this is kind of exciting.
我们的名字会永远...
Our names will forever be shrouded...
Ted,Ted,Ted\nTed,Ted,Ted.
看, 我钓到了个伴娘
Look,I got a bridesmaid.
Ted, 看, 看, Ted, 第二辣的伴娘
Ted,look,look,Ted,the second hottest bridesmaid.
Ted,看
Ted,look.
再见咯,Ted
See ya,Ted.
恩,我是Ted.
So,I'm Ted.
Victoria\nVictoria.
不要说姓
But no last names.
不说姓
No last names.
你有问题啊?
what is wrong with you?
伙计, 那就象...
Dude,that is just,like...
个烂点子
a weenie-ass idea.
不, 那很棒
No,it was awesome
我有个很棒的夜晚
I had a great night,
我再也不会见到她
I'm never gonna see her again,
没人能破坏那一晚
and there's no way to ruin it.
Ted, 我该怎么跟你说?
Ted,how do I explain this to you?
昨晚我吃了这辈子吃过最好吃的蛋糕
Last night I ate the best cake of my life.
现在, 你想让我再也吃不到了吗?
Now,you think I'm gonna let that cake\nout of my life?
天, 不要 我要找到是谁做的那蛋糕
Hell,no.I'm gonna find out what bakery\nmade that cake,
然后我要弄多点蛋糕来
and then I'm gonna get some more cake.
那蛋糕真的很吸引你?
That cake really got to you?
它勾引我
It haunts me.
恩, 后来怎么了?
So,what happened next?
好了
Okay.
基本规则已经建立了
Ground rules have been established.
现在让我看看你说了那么多的行动怎么进行
Now let's see some of these moves I've heard\nso much about.
等等,等等
Wait,wait,wait,wait,wait.
我们来做所有单身女性都想在婚礼上干的偷走花球
Let's do all the single ladies in this joint a big favor and steal the bouquet.
好, 但我们得...
Yes,but we'll need...
分散大家注意力
a diversion.
接吻!
kiss!
吻! 吻, 来一个!
Kiss! Kiss,come on!
接吻! 接吻! 接吻!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
走, 走, 快走
Go,go,go,go,go,go,go.
那就是花球的下落
So that's what happened to the bouquet.
你知道, Victoria干的好
You know,good for Victoria.
真是邪恶的传统
It's such an evil tradition.
你不会在你的婚礼上抛花球?
You're not gonna do it at your wedding?
天, 我要拿起那束花弹
Hell,I'm gonna take that flower-grenade
甩到人群里然后大叫
and chuck it into the crowd and scream,
"爬过来抢吧, 婊子们!"
"crawl for it,bitches!"
那就是女孩们想做的
That's just what girls do.
那么, 你们两去哪了?
So,where'd you guys go?
很不错\n是吗?
very nice.\nYeah?
好吧, 我其实不知道怎么跳踢踏舞
Okay,I don't really know how to tap dance.
我也分不出来
I couldn't tell.
真的
Really.
今晚我们不能怎么样太遗憾了
it's too bad you're not gonna get some tonight.
如果我想, 我就能
if I wanted some,I could get some.
不, 你不能
No,you couldn't.
你是个男人
You're a dude.
- 我能干什么\n- 你完全能干点什么
- I could get some.\n- You could totally get some.
我们今晚不能接吻
We're not gonna kiss tonight.
如果 如果我们接吻了
if if we kiss,
所有这些都会变的现实
all of this becomes real.
你 你可能舌头伸太长
You you might use too much tongue.
我可能伸的不够长
I might not use enough.
然后突然,这些被破坏
And then suddenly,poof,spell's broken.
我舌头在你嘴里会用的恰倒好处的
I will use exactly the right amount of tongue.
好吧, 这样怎么样?
Okay,how about this?
任何初吻的最棒部分都是引发的过程
The best part of any first kiss is the\nlead-up to it.
嘴唇接触到的前一刻
The moment right before the lips touch.
就象前奏锣鼓
It's like a big drumroll.
所以...
So...
今晚
how about tonight,
我们只进行到前奏怎么样?
we just stick with the drumroll?
好吧
Okay.
但我们不能接吻
But we can't kiss.
好吧
Okay.
前奏锣鼓?
A drumroll?
对
That's it
所以, 那, 你就...
so,what,you just...
你就说晚安, 回家...
you said good night,came home and...
独自敲鼓?
performed a drum solo?
Ted, 你这个蠢家伙!
Ted,you're such a doof!
我是说, 这女孩听起来那么棒
I mean,this girl sounds amazing.
她确实很棒
She was completely amazing.
她还很幽默
She was amazing and funny,
我们很合拍
and we connected on every level,
而且我们再也不会见面了
and I'm never gonna see her again.
该死, 我得再见到她!
Damn it,I have to see her again!
对! 对!
Yes! Yes!
行动起来吧, 兄弟
So let's get to work,man.
关于她你还知道什么?
What else do you know about her?
什么也没了 她叫Victoria
Nothing.Her name's Victoria
这就是全部我知道的
that's all I got.
等下, Claudia, Claudia知道
Wait,Claudia,Claudia would know.
Claudia正在渡蜜月
Claudia's on her honeymoon.
她两周后会回来 那时候打给她
She'll be back in two weeks,call her then.
好, 两周
Yes,two weeks.
好主意
Good idea.
我现在就打给她
I'm calling her now.
别, Ted, 你不会去搞砸蜜月的
No,Ted,you don't mess with a honeymoon.
来吧, 伙计
come on,dude.
问下她蛋糕
Ask her about the cake.
Ted?\nTed?
嘿，Claudia!
Hey,Claudia!
盛大的婚礼, 美妙的祝酒词, 美味的食物
Great wedding,beautiful toast,touching stuff.
蜜月怎么样?
How's the honeymoon?
听着, 我打电话是因为昨晚我遇到一个女孩
Listen,I'm calling because last night\nI met this girl,
我在想你是否知道...
and I was wondering if you had...
你在开我玩笑吧!
you have got to be freaking kidding me!
又来了
here we go.
24小时前, 你还求我...
24 hours ago,you were begging...
求我带另个女孩参加我婚礼
begging me to bring some other girl to my wedding,
现在
and now,
你就和她分了?
you're over her?
我向前走了?
I've moved on?
她叫什么?
What was her name?
是我的胖堂妹Lindsay吗?
Is it my fat cousin Lindsay?
别觉得尴尬 她眼睛很美
Don't be embarrassed,she has pretty eyes.
不是
no.
她叫Victoria
Her name was Victoria.
我不知道她姓什么
I don't know her last name.
幸运的是
lucky for you,
我知道嘉宾名单上的每一个人
I know that guest list backwards and forwards.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
不幸的是
Unlucky for you,
我婚礼上没有叫Victoria的人
there was no Victoria at my wedding.
再见, Ted
Goodbye,Ted.
婚礼上没有叫Victoria的
There was no Victoria at the wedding.
可能她用了第二个假名
Maybe she used a second fake name.
她真行
she's good,
她真是行啊
she's very good.
也许她是个幽灵
Maybe she was ghost.
这就是为什么她不吻你
That's why she didn't want to kiss you
因为你会穿过她的身体感觉到一丝凉意
because you'd just pass right through her \nand feel really cold for a second.
我的天, 我刚想出了个绝妙的剧本
my god,I just had a great idea for a screenplay.
Marshall...\nMarshall...
她不是幽灵!
she was not a ghost!
我知道她不是幽灵
I know that she wasn't a ghost.
她把花球拿起来了,说明她有肉体
She picked up a bouquet,proving she had corporeal form.
等等!
Wait,wait!
她坐在伴娘的对面
She was sitting across from a couple\nof bridesmaids.
她一定在那桌
She must've been at their table.
也许她们知道她是谁
Maybe they know who she was.
太好了
Great.
所以我们怎么找到伴娘呢?
So how do we get in touch with the bridesmaids?
这太棒了
this better be good
我快飞上天堂了
I am about to enter Nirvana.
顺便说下, 我应该给你涅磐的电话
By the way,I should get you Nirvana's\nphone number.
她按摩太棒了
She gives a great massage.
说什么?!
Say what?!
Barney!\nBarney!
我知道这的规矩
I know the house rules.
Es un chiste!\nEs un chiste!
听着, Barney
Listen,Barney,
我看见你昨晚和个伴娘一起
I saw you talking to that bridesmaid last night.
你有没拿到她电话?
Did you happen to get her phone number?
你知道我有
You know I did.
太棒了!
Great!
我要你为我给她打电话
I'm gonna need you to call her for me.
不知道我不会
You know I won't.
为什么?
Why not?
因为我们只是昨晚一起
Because we just hooked up last night.
我不会第二天就给她打电话
I can't call the girl the next day.
我得等到至少, 大概...
I have to wait at least,like...
永远
forever.
噢 咔嚓! 永远也不打给她
Oh,snap! Never gonna call her.
而且, 她以为我在去印度的路上
Besides,she thinks I'm on my way to India.
拜托, Barney, 这次理由很充分
come on,Barney,it's for a good cause,
Ted搞砸了那么多次和女孩一起,这绝对不是个好理由
Ted going all castrati over yet another girl\nis exactly not a good cause.
抱歉, 兄弟,我希望我能帮你但我的手被绑住了
Sorry,buddy,I wish I could help you, my hands are tied.
等等
wait
那是昨晚
that was last night.
好吧, Barney, 我来告诉你我会做什么
okay,Barney,I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
你打这个电话我就和你一起去看女子拳击
You make this call and I will go with you\nto Foxy Boxing.
- 真的吗?\n- 是的。
- Really?\n- Yeah.
但你老是说女子拳击既没吸引力也打的不好
But you always said the Foxy Boxing girls were neither foxy not good at boxing.
我准备好去证明我是错的
I'm ready to be proven wrong.
今晚?
Tonight?
今晚
Tonight.
打吧
Dial.
Tanya, 事实证明知道明天我才参加和平队
Tanya,turns out I don't leave for the Peace Corps till tomorrow.
是的，我知道
Yeah,I know.
很糟糕
It sucks.
我去帮助人的日子又少了一天
Just one fewer day I get to help people.
无论如何, 这女孩 知道她是谁吗?
Anyway,this girl,any idea who she was?
等等
Hold on.
她穿什么样的鞋...
What kind of shoes was sh...
不, Tanya, 他是个男的
no,Tanya,he's a dude.
他不会注意她穿什么样的鞋
He's not gonna know what kind of shoes\nshe was wearing.
事实上...
Actually...
拜托
come on.
接下来想做什么?
So what do you want to do next?
别考虑
don't think.
脑海里浮现出的第一件事
First thing that comes into your mind.
拿着...
hold...
这个...
this...
还有这个...
and this...
噢 她真厉害
Oh There she goes.
显然她穿着棕色...
Apparently she was wearing brown shoes...
...上面装饰着雪花
...with little snowflakes on them.
是啊 听起来是很可爱
Yeah they do sound cute.
知道是谁...?
Any idea who...?
好吧
Okay.
还是谢谢你
thanks anyway.
你保重...
you take ca...
什么...?
what's...?
今晚?
Tonight?
我明天很早就要起航
I'm shipping out pretty early,
所以我大概不能过夜了
so I won't be able to stay over,
但,耶，当然 我很乐意
but,yeah,sure,I'd love to.
好的 晚点找你
Okay. I'll talk to you later.
抱歉, Ted,我今晚不能去看女子拳击了
Sorry,Ted,I won't be able to make\nfoxy Boxing tonight.
我理解
I understand.
好吧, 别灰心
Okay,let's not lose hope.
我们打到酒店去
We'll call the hotel.
也许她还在那
Maybe she was staying there.
我们可以让他们查下入住名单看有么叫Victoria的
We'll have them check the registry for anyone named Victoria.
也许她叫Vicky或者Tori...
Or maybe she goes by Vicky or Tori...
或者Ictor
or Ictor.
她当然不叫Ictor
She probably doesn't go by "Ictor."
不, 你知道吗?
No,you know what?
这就是命运
This is fate.
我再也见不到那女孩了
I am never supposed to see this girl again.
这就是昨晚的重点
That was the whole point of the night.
我注定一个人
I have just been saved from myself.
我们来狂饮吧
Let's drink many beers.
同意
Agreed.
我以为就那样结束了
And I thought that was the end of it.
但是后来...
But then...
嘿 我们的女主持人!
There's the anchor lady!
主持的怎么样?
How was it?
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么不问问新来的代打女主持?
Why don't you ask the new substitute\nweend anchor?
Robin?\nRobin?
谢谢, Robin!
Thanks,Robin!
太棒了
It was awesome.
支持你, Robin
Back to you,Robin.
恭喜!
Congrats!
太酷了!
That's so cool!
但我对放了Ted鸽子感到很抱歉
I felt really bad bailing on Ted,though.
不用担心了
don't even worry about it.
事实上...
In fact...
然后Lily告诉了她整个故事
and then Lily told her the whole story,
包括她穿的棕色带着雪花装饰的鞋
right down to the brown shoes with\nthe little snowflakes on them.
然后最后...
And by the end of it...
什么?
what?
我知道她是谁
I know who she is.
你知道她是谁?
You know who she is?
但你甚至没有参加婚礼
But you weren't even at the wedding.
事实上, 某种程度上... 我参加了
Actually,I kind of... was.
什么?
What?
新闻结束后
after the newscast,
我很激动 决定去婚礼给Ted一个惊喜
I was so excited I decided to surprise Ted\nby going to the reception.
该死!
damn it!
别哭!
stop it!
到底怎么了!
what the hell!
你好?
Hello?
你还好吧?
You okay in there?
我很好
I'm fine.
只是过敏或者别的什么
just allergies or something.
我很好
I'm fine.
听着, 你...
Listen,do you...
想出来放声大哭吗?
want to come and cry out here?
我被告知是个不错的安慰者
I've been told I'm an excellent hugger.
谢谢
thanks.
但我不会在人前哭泣...
but I don't actually cry in front of\npeople or...
或者根本不会为了这种事哭
cry at all,for that matter.
天, 好恶心
man,it's gross.
每个人哭的时候都会流那么多鼻涕吗?
Does everyone snot up this much when they cry?
你在和一个同样的鼻涕虫说话
you're speaking to a fellow snotter.
恩, 你为什么哭?
so,why are you crying?
因为你喜欢Ted
Because you have feelings for Ted.
我不知道
I don't know.
也许?
Maybe?
好了, 你们两个到底怎么了!
Okay,what is wrong with the two of you!
说真的!
Seriously!
他喜欢你你喜欢他
He likes you and you like him.
那就在一起就好了!
And j...j...just be together!
我的天那!
Cheese louise!
幸福没那么困难吧!
Happiness is not that difficult!
听着, 好吧, 是的
Look,okay,yes.
我在卫生间里哭而且...
I cried in the bathroom and that...
那很怪
was weird.
但并不表示我喜欢上了那家伙
But that doesn't mean I'm in love with the guy.
事实是, 我 我不知道我的感觉
The fact is,I...I don't know how I feel.
不, 你知道!
Yes,you do!
看见他和别人在一起然后哭泣?
Seeing him with someone else and crying about it?
猜怎样?
Guess what?
这就是你有感觉
That's how you feel.
这绝对就是你有感觉
That is nothing but how you feel.
好了, 好吧
Okay,fine.
我对他有感觉 高兴了?
I have feelings for him. Happy?
可以说, 是啊
Kinda,yeah.
但这并不能改变什么
But it doesn't change anything.
我还是不想结婚他仍然是... Ted
I still don't want to get married and he's\nstill...Ted.
我要做的就是告诉他谁是Victoria让他开心
What I should do is just tell him who\nVictoria is so he can be happy.
或者你告诉他你喜欢他,然后你们两个都开心了
Or you could tell him that you're into him and then you could both be happy.
我现在去找他
I'm gonna go find him.
等下
wait
你要告诉他哪一个?
which one are you going to tell him?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
然后就是最精彩的部分了
And here's the most amazing part
因为我告诉他我把所有的钱都换成印度币了
because I told her I'd converted all\nmy money to India dollars,
她就给了我50块坐计程车去机场
she gave me 50 bucks to take a cab to the airport.
对了
That's right.
我靠做爱挣钱了
I just got paid for sex.
我真的该把这钱捐给和平队
I really should give this money to the \nPeace Corps.
他们最近为我做了这么多好事
They've done so much for me lately.
嗨, 伙计们
Hi,guys.
Ted, 我能和你在外面聊几句吗?
Ted,can I talk to you outside for a second?
当然
sure.
怎么了?
What's up?
我, 我有事得告诉你
I,I have to tell you something.
接电话吧
just get it.
喂?
Hello?
Ted?\nTed?
我是Stuart
It's Stuart.
我可爱的新娘有话对你说
My lovely bride would like to say something\nto you.
Ted...\nTed...
很抱歉我之前挂你电话
I'm sorry I hung up on you earlier.
我的新婚丈夫
My new husband,
还有草莓伏特加
and the vodka cranberry,
在鬼机场花了$10.50...
which cost $10.50 at the freakin' airport bar...
这航班什么时候才开始登机啊?!
when is this plane going to board?!
小甜豆?
Sweet pea?
...让我意识到
...have helped me realize that
有时候我象个疯子
sometimes I can act like a crazy person,
我不想我的丈夫认为我是个疯子
and I don't want my new husband to think\nI'm a crazy person.
没事, Claudia, 别担心
It's fine,Claudia,don't worry about it.
Marshall想知道你们在哪买的蛋糕
Marshall wanted to know where you guys got\nthat cake.
蛋糕?
The cake?
把这个拿着?
Why don't you take this?
似乎你比较需要
Sounds like you could use it.
谢谢
Thanks.
你真贴心
you're very sweet.
你是新娘还是新郎的朋友?
So are you a friend of the bride or groom?
我们在市区一个小面包房买的
We got it at this little bakery downtown.
事实上都不是
Actually neither.
叫奶油花面包房
It's called the Buttercup Bakery.
很高兴认识你, 奶油花
Pleased to meet you,Buttercup.
我是做蛋糕的
I made the cake.
她是做蛋糕的
She made the cake.
奶油花面包房...她不在嘉宾名单上是因为她不是嘉宾,她是做蛋糕的
Buttercup Bakery...she wasn't on the guest list because she wasn't a guest.She made the cake
她做的蛋糕?Ted, 就是她了
She made that cake?Ted,this is the girl.
你得娶了她
You got to marry her.
就今天
Today.
她得搬来和我们一起住
She has to move in with us.
我现在就去那个面包房
I'm going down to that bakery.
别, 别 别去
No,no. Don't do it.
宝贝, 你在说什么呢?!
Baby,what are you talking about?!
整天你都在帮忙想办法找那个女孩
all day long you been busting my apple-bag\nabout finding this girl.
我 我只是在想...
I-I just think that...
也许她不是那么喜欢你
that maybe she's not that into you.
这就是为什么她没有给你留电话
And-and that's why she didn't give you\nher number.
Robin?\nRobin?
有什么补充的吗?
Care to chime in with anything?
好
Yes.
Ted...\nTed...
去找她吧
go get her.
去吧
Going.
去找她
Getting.
Ted, 噢, 我的天, 我喜欢这一刻
Ted,oh,my,gosh,I love this moment.
知道为什么吗? 因我要说
You know why? Cause I'm going to say it,
这次, 你准备好说好了吗
and this time,you're actually going to say yes.
准备好了吗? 准备好说好了吗?
You ready?You ready to say yes?
Ted, 穿上礼服
Ted,suit up.
好!
Yes!
不
no.
拜托!
come on!
看起来我们离开有一会了
Guess we were gone a while.
这太可惜了
that's too bad.
我很期待最后那支舞呢
I was looking forward to one last dance.
为什么, 是啊, 我是
why,yes,I am.
抱歉, 我可以看出你在想什么
Sorry,I could tell what you were just thinking.
我刚在想什么?
what was I just thinking?
"该死, 他穿这礼服太棒了"
"Damn,he's looking mighty fine in that tux."
你说对了
you got me.
你真不错
You are good.
你知道, 我并不是每天都这样穿
You know,I don't look like this every day.
在现实的周末
On a real weekend,
现实里的Ted穿着牛仔裤和洗的发白的T恤
the real Ted wears a pair of jeans and\na sweatshirt with bleach stains on it.
现实里的Ted听起来很性感
The real Ted sounds real sexy.
我再也看不到你太可惜了
Too bad I'll never get to see it.
奶油花面包房
Buttercup Bakery.
就这了
This is it.
祝你好运, 伙计
Good luck,dude.
给我弄块蛋糕来
Grab me a cupcake.
Ted?\nTed?
你有听我们说吗?
You still with us?
告诉我你的姓
tell me your last name.
你知道我们的计划里有点缺陷
You know there's one little flaw in our plan.
那是什么?
What's that?
我们会带着许多美好回忆
I'm going to go home tonight with a lot \nof great memories
和一个烂回忆回家
and one really sucky memory.
那就是我看着你走掉的回忆
The memory of you walking out that door.
嘿，Ted
Hey,Ted.
闭上眼...
Close your eyes...
数到5
and count to five.
1...\nOne...
2...\ntwo...
3...\nthree...
4...\nfour...
5\nfive.
直到我们死去
And to our dying days
我们也会记得这个完美的夜晚
we'll remember everything about that night\nas perfect.
也许我们都需要那样
Maybe we both need that.
我是说, 生活里有那么多不如意
I mean,so many things go wrong in life
但有一件永远不会被破坏
but this is the one thing that never will.
它将会...
It will always...
永远纯净不被污染
always be pure unadulterated awesome.
但如果我走进那里
And if I walk in there,
我就会把它夺走...
I'm robbing both of us...
出租车计费器还在走呢, 伙计
the meter's running,dude.
抓住机会
Crap or get off the pot.
我去了
I'm going.
噢, 谢天谢地
Oh,thank god.
老爸老妈的浪漫史\n第1季 第13集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother\nSeason 01 Episode 13